Inventory of the Nell Eurich papers 1922-2000
Hoover Institution Archives
- Education, training, and technology file
  - Partnerships
    - New Jersey Department of Higher Education, business and humanities project, 1986-1988 (Box-folder 69: 11)
    - Phi Delta Kappan, 1980-1982 (Box-folder 69: 12)
    - Rhodes, Frank H. T., testimony concerning industry and academia, 1987 (Box-folder 69: 13)
    - School and business partnerships, 1985-1988 (Box-folder 69: 14)
    - State University of New York Business Development Service, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 69: 15)
    - Thomas A. Edison State College Center for Corporate Partnerships, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 70: 1)
    - United States Information Agency project, "Academia and the Corporate World,", 1985 (Box-folder 70: 2)
  - International education and training
    - Australian Institute of Management, Peter Peterson, 1987 (Box-folder 70: 3)
    - Belgium, Gaston Deurinck, Foundation Industrie-Universite, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 70: 4)
    - Bing, John, 1987 (Box-folder 70: 5)
      Includes proposal concerning training for international managers
    - Blackburn, David, 1986 (Box-folder 70: 6)
      Includes materials on International Technological University
    - Budd, Herbert, "Networking and Development,", 1987 (Box-folder 70: 7)
    - China, Beijing Vacuum Electronics Research Institute, undated (Box-folder 70: 8)
    - Community Action Programme for Education and Training for Technology (COMETT), 1986-1987 (Box-folder 70: 9)
    - European Foundation for Management Development
      - General, 1984-1987 (Box-folder 70: 10-11)
      - 15th Anniversary Meeting, 1986 (Box-folder 70: 12)
    - European Institute of Education and Social Policy, Ladislav Cerych, 1984-1986 (Box-folder 71: 1)
    - European Programme of Advanced Continuing Education (PACE), Barry Arnett and Ladislav Cerych, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 71: 2)
- The Learning Industry and Adult Learning Project file
  - Vendors
    - Distance education and delivery systems
      - Corporation for Public Broadcasting (CPB)
        - Statistics, bibliographies, and articles, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 71: 3)
        - Other literature, 1985-1986, undated (Box-folder 71: 4)
        - CPB Report, 1987-1989 (Box-folder 71: 5)
        - Annenberg/CPB project, 1984-1987, undated (Box-folder 71: 6)
      - Public Broadcasting Service (PBS)
        - Memorandum and overviews, 1987 (Box-folder 71: 7)
        - Adult Learning Services, 1985-1988 (Box-folder 72: 1)
        - National Narrowcast Service, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 72: 2)
        - Video catalogs and newsletters, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 72: 3)
      - Electronic University Network, 1983-1987 (Box-folder 72: 4)
      - Focus Media Inc., circa 1988 (Box-folder 72: 5)
      - Institute of Electrical and Electronic Engineers (IEEE), 1987-1988 (Box-folder 72: 6)
      - Learning Channel, 1987 (Box-folder 72: 7)
      - National Center for Development Education, undated (Box-folder 72: 8)
      - National Technological University (NTU)
        - Memoranda on telephones, 1987 (Box-folder 73: 1)
        - General, 1983-1988 (Box-folder 73: 2-3)
        - Articles, 1987-1989 (Box-folder 73: 4)
        - NTUplink, 1988-1999 (Box-folder 73: 5)
        - NTU News, 1985-1989 (Box-folder 73: 6)
        - Annual reports and brochures, 1986-1989 (Box-folder 73: 7)
        - Bulletins, 1985 (Box-folder 73: 8)
        - Class schedules, 1984-1989 (Box-folder 73: 9)
      - Non-Profit Network, 1987 (Box-folder 73: 10)
      - Public Interest Video Network, 1987 (Box-folder 73: 11)
      - TRAINET, American Society for Training and Development (ASTD), 1987 (Box-folder 73: 12)
      - Western Behavioral Sciences Institute (WESI), 1987-1988 (Box-folder 74: 1)
  - Unions
    - General, 1986-1992 (Box-folder 74: 2)
    - Articles, 1986-1988 (Box-folder 74: 3)
    - AFL-CIO
      - General, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 74: 4)
      - Educational Update newsletters, 1986-1988 (Box-folder 74: 5)
      - Training and Education Conference, 1986 (Box-folder 74: 6)
    - Other literature
      - University and College Labor Education Association (UCLEA), 1986-1987 (Box-folder 74: 7)
- Education, training, and technology file
  - International education and training
    - Finland, 1985 (Box-folder 74: 8)
    - French-American Foundation, 1985, undated (Box-folder 74: 9)
    - French Embassy science mission, 1986 (Box-folder 74: 10)
    - Great Britain
      - Manpower Services Commission, Michael Beck, 1988 (Box-folder 74: 11)
      - Pilkington Group and Lakeside Training Services, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 74: 12)
    - International Business Machines (IBM)/Hewlett-Packard US-European forum on continuing education, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 75: 1)
      Includes speech by Nell Eurich
    - International Business Machines (IBM) South Africa, Betty McCormick, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 75: 2)
    - Instituto Colombiano de Estudios Superiores de Incolda (ICESI), Alfonso Ocampo, 1992-1995, undated (Box-folder 75: 3)
    - Interclass, James Botkin, 1990-1996 (Box-folder 75: 4)
    - Joint Universities and Polytechnics Industrial Technology Education and Research (JUPITER), Jean Millar, 1986 (Box-folder 75: 5)
    - Pakistan
      - Assessment programs, 1986 (Box-folder 75: 6)
      - Pakistan-Habib Group, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 75: 7)
    - Swedish National Board of Education
      - Implementing Recurrent Education in Sweden, 1988 (Box-folder 75: 8)
      - Division of Adult Education, Kenneth Abrahamsson, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 75: 9)
    - UNESCO, 1988 (Box-folder 75: 10)
  - Technology
    - General technology and computers
      - Articles, 1966-1991 (Box-folder 75: 11)
      - Shepard, Susan, articles and correspondence, 1984-1987 (Box-folder 75: 12)
        Includes artificial intelligence (AI) material
      - Resources on artificial intelligence (AI), 1985-1988 (Box-folder 76: 1)
    - Educational technology
      - Resources
        - Distance learning and distance education, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 76: 2)
        - Historical background on computers in learning and society, 1982-1984 (Box-folder 76: 3)
          Includes materials on Sweden
        - Instructional technology, 1985-1987 (Box-folder 76: 4)
        - Learning technology conferences, 1985-1987 (Box-folder 76: 5)
          Includes material related to Europe
        - Learning theory, 1987, undated (Box-folder 77: 1)
        - Preparatory material, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 77: 2)
      - Birendaum, Helen, Stanton/Heiskell Center for Public Policy in Telecommunications and Information Systems and New York City Partnerships, Inc., 1984-1988 (Box-folder 77: 3)
      - Dunham, E. Alden, "Educational Reform: The Critical Role of Information Technology,", 1991 (Box-folder 77: 4)
        Includes correspondence
      - DeCarlo, Charles R., Electronic Operating Systems Corporation, 1985 (Box-folder 77: 5)
      - Institute for Learning Technologies, 1986 (Box-folder 77: 6)
      - McNeil, Donald R., 1988-1989 (Box-folder 77: 7)
      - National Commission on Industrial Innovation, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 77: 8)
      - Oettinger, Anthony G., Harvard University program on information resources policy, 1989 (Box-folder 77: 9)
      - Open University, England, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 77: 10)
      - Performax, John Barwick, 1986 (Box-folder 77: 11)
      - Roberts, Walter Orr, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 77: 12)
      - Telecommunications education consultants, 1988 (Box-folder 77: 13)
      - Texas Instruments AI Satellite Symposium, 1987 (Box-folder 77: 14)
  - Future
    - "What the Next 50 Years Will Bring," US News & World Report, 1983 (Box-folder 77: 15)
- The Learning Industry and Adult Learning Project file
  - Research files for The Learning Project
    - Target groups
      - Missing persons
        - Displacement
          - General, 1987 (Box-folder 77: 16)
          - Research studies, 1986, undated (Box-folder 77: 17)
          - Industrial Adjustment Service Unit, Department of Labor, 1983-1987 (Box-folder 77: 18)
          - Displaced workers, 1986-1988 (Box-folder 78: 1)
          - Outplacement, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 78: 2)
          - White collar displacement, 1987 (Box-folder 78: 3)
      - Temporary workers, 1987-1993 (Box-folder 78: 4)
  - Technology and training
    - Distance education and delivery systems
      - General, 1986-1988 (Box-folder 78: 5)
      - Articles, 1983-1989 (Box-folder 78: 6)
      - Research studies
        - General, 1984-1986 (Box-folder 78: 7)
        - Assessing Long-Distance Learning via Telecommunications, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 78: 8)
        - Annenberg/Corporation for Public Broadcasting (CPB) project, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 78: 9)
        - Davis Jenkins report draft from August 1988 (Box-folder 79: 1)
          Includes drafts of Part III (Technologies for Learning in the Information Age), appendices, and case studies. Possibly part of a draft The Learning Project.
        - Davis Jenkins, general material, 1987 (Box-folder 79: 2)
      - Other literature
        - General, 1984-1987 (Box-folder 79: 3)
        - American Journal of Distance Education, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 79: 4)
        - Technology Transfer Institute, catalogs, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 79: 5-6)
        - Teletraining newsletters, 1987 (Box-folder 79: 67)
        - Conference brochures, 1986-1988 (Box-folder 79: 8)
        - Consortia lists and notes, 1987 (Box-folder 79: 9)
      - Printed matter related to training videotapes, 1987 (Box-folder 80: 1)
      - Video teleconferencing, 1988 (Box-folder 80: 2)
      - Artificial intelligence (AI)
        - Bibliography and intelligent computer-assisted instruction (ICAI) examples, Susan Shepard, 1988 (Box-folder 80: 3)
        - Articles, 1985-1989 (Box-folder 80: 4)
        - Research study by Carnegie Commission on Higher Education, The Fourth Revolution, 1972 (Box-folder 80: 5)
        - AI material not used (draft by Susan Shepard), undated (Box-folder 80: 6)
        - Other literature
          - General, 1985-1988 (Box-folder 80: 7)
          - David Kolb's Learning Style Inventory, 1981-1986 (Box-folder 80: 8)
          - Gold Hill Applications Portfolio, 1988 (Box-folder 80: 9)
        - Intelligent computer-assisted instruction (ICAI) in the military, memoranda, 1987 (Box-folder 80: 10)
  - Education
    - General
      - Articles, 1987-1989 (Box-folder 80: 11)
      - Research studies, 1985-1989 (Box-folder 80: 12)
      - "Beyond the Rhetoric,", 1988 (Box-folder 80: 13)
        Report on university/industry research
  - Drafts and notes for The Learning Industry
    - Complete draft, undated (Box-folder 81: 1-2)
    - Complete draft on floppy disks, undated (Box-folder 81: 3)
      Nine floppy disks. Includes paper copy of description of contents.
    - Endnotes, figures, and tables
      - Prologue: The Challenge of Change
        - Endnotes (source material), 1985-1989 (Box-folder 82: 1)
        - Material not used in notes, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 82: 2)
      - Chapter I: Classrooms for Adults
        - Endnotes (source material), 1987-1990 (Box-folder 82: 3)
        - Table 1, 1988 (Box-folder 82: 4)
        - Material not used in notes, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 82: 5)
      - Chapter II: Delivering Instruction
        - Endnotes (source material), 1988-1989 (Box-folder 82: 6)
        - Table 2, 1990, undated (Box-folder 82: 7)
        - Graphics not used, undated (Box-folder 82: 8)
        - Material not used in notes, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 82: 9)
      - Chapter III: The Intelligent Tutor
        - Endnotes (source material), 1985-1989 (Box-folder 82: 10)
        - Material not used in notes, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 82: 11)
      - Chapter IV: Training Technical Workers
        - Endnotes (source material), 1985-1988 (Box-folder 82: 12)
        - Materials not used in notes, 1985-1989 (Box-folder 83: 1-2)
      - Chapter V: Educating Managers
        - Endnotes (source material), 1984-1989 (Box-folder 83: 3-4)
        - Figures and tables, 1985, undated (Box-folder 83: 5)
        - Material not used in notes, 1986-1989 (Box-folder 83: 6)
      - Chapter VI: Updating Professionals
        - Endnotes (source material), 1959-1989 (Box-folder 84: 1)
        - Material not used in notes, 1986-1989 (Box-folder 84: 2)
- Professional positions and activities file
  - Vassar College
    - Publications, 1966-1971 (Box-folder 84: 3)
    - Correspondence, 1969-1971 (Box-folder 84: 4)
    - Board minutes, 1966-1968 (Box-folder 84: 5)
    - Board minutes, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 85: 1)
    - Comprehensive Planning Committee, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 85: 2)
    - Comprehensive plan, 1968 (Box-folder 85: 3)
    - "The Record at Vassar College,", 1970 (Box-folder 85: 4)
      Compiled by Nell Eurich
    - Attachments for "The Record at Vassar,", 1967-1970 (Box-folder 86: 1-2)
    - Dean of faculty reports to Board of Trustees and Executive Committee, 1967-1969 (Box-folder 86: 3)
    - Annual reports, dean of the faculty, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 87: 1)
    - Steering Committee, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 87: 2)
- Speeches and writings
  - Speeches
    Includes correspondence and conference material
    - "Educating the Work Force in the Year 2025," International Council for Educational Development, 1993 June (Box-folder 87: 3)
    - "Continuing Education and the Learning Industry," Pennsylvania State University, 1991 June 25 (Box-folder 87: 4)
      Includes materials from 1990 and 1991
    - "The Learning Industry: Education for Adult Workers," Chicago Seminars on the Future, 1990 November (Box-folder 87: 5)
    - "Adult Learning for Productivity," The Education Summit: A Conference on Lifespan Learning, George Mason University, 1988 June (Box-folder 87: 6)
    - "Training for Productivity," Second Basque World Conference on Current problems in Economic Science, 1987 September 18
      - Final version, 1987 (Box-folder 88: 1)
      - Drafts and correspondence, 1986-1988 (Box-folder 88: 2)
      - General, 1985-1987 (Box-folder 88: 3)
      - Conference material and printed matter, 1987 (Box-folder 88: 4)
    - "Remarks on Corporate Classrooms," DEC, 1987 May 27 (Box-folder 88: 5)
    - "Corporate Classrooms: The Learning Business," 15th Anniversary Meeting of the European Foundation for Management Development, 1986 October 24 (Box-folder 88: 6)
    - "Learning Networks," IBM/Hewlett-Packard Forum, 1986 September 23 (Box-folder 88: 7)
    - "Corporate Classrooms: Why Companies Have Their Own," College Board Seminar, 1986 April 3 (Box-folder 88: 8)
    - "Corporations and Colleges," Manhattanville College, 1986 February and May (Box-folder 88: 9)
    - "The Next Twenty-Five Years," Point Park College, 25th Anniversary Convocation, 1985 November 21 (Box-folder 88: 10)
    - "Corporate Classrooms Pose Issues for Higher Education," North Carolina Association of College and University Presidents, 1985 October 31 (Box-folder 88: 11)
    - "Learning and Technology," IBM Seminar on Education Technology, 1985 July (Box-folder 88: 12)
    - "Education in the Workplace," Teachers College, Columbia University, 1985 June 7 (Box-folder 89: 1)
    - "Implications of Corporate Classrooms," Brookings Institution, 1985 May 7 (Box-folder 89: 2)
    - "Corporate Classrooms: the Learning Business," Northwest Regional Conference of Danforth Associates, 1985 April 26 (Box-folder 89: 3)
    - "Focus on the Corporate Role in Education," AT&T Technologies, 1985 April 2 (Box-folder 89: 4)
    - "Review of Corporate Classrooms for School Superintendents," Northwestern University Consortium of School Districts, 1985 March 19 (Box-folder 89: 5)
    - "The Private Sector," American Council on Education Program for the Advancement of Women in Higher Education Administration, Brooklyn Region Conference, 1981 May 8 (Box-folder 89: 6)
    - "Women in Higher Education," Women's City Club of Cleveland, 1978 March 22 (Box-folder 89: 7)
      Includes research materials from 1971 to 1978
    - Speeches, 1968-1977 (Box-folder 89: 8)
- Professional positions and activities file
  - Cambridge College, 1980-2000 (Box-folder 89: 9)
    Eurich was a member of the Academic Advisory Board
  - Alliance for Learning, 1985-1990 (Box-folder 90: 1)
  - Vassar College
    - Appointment
      - Terms, 1966 (Box-folder 90: 2)
      - Letters and clippings, 1966 (Box-folder 90: 3)
    - Vassar and Yale
      - Clippings and miscellany, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 90: 4)
      - "Short of Total Relocation" draft, 1967 (Box-folder 90: 5)
      - Statements and reports on Vassar and Yale, 1967 (Box-folder 90: 6)
      - Vassar-Yale Study drafts, 1967 (Box-folder 90: 7)
      - Evelyn Clark statement, 1967 (Box-folder 90: 8)
      - Correspondence with John Wilkie and others, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 90: 9)
    - Nell Eurich file
      - Speeches, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 90: 10)
      - Personal letters, 1967-1969 (Box-folder 91: 1)
      - Publicity, 1966-1968 (Box-folder 91: 2)
        Includes photographs of Eurich speaking
      - Writings by Eurich, 1967, undated (Box-folder 91: 3)
    - Administration
      - Alumnae and clubs, 1968-1970 (Box-folder 91: 4)
      - Enrollment projections, 1969 (Box-folder 91: 5)
      - Budget, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 91: 6)
      - Budget crisis, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 91: 7)
      - Middle States Association case study, 1969 (Box-folder 91: 8)
      - Faculty handbook and related materials, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 91: 9)
    - Black Studies
      - Faculty actions, 1969 (Box-folder 91: 10)
        Includes chronology of events
    - General
      - Vassar Alumnae Magazine, 1967-1969 (Box-folder 91: 11)
      - Coeducation, 1969 (Box-folder 91: 12)
      - Third Minnewaska Conference, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 91: 13)
    - Curricular reforms
      - General, 1968-1970 (Box-folder 91: 14)
      - Forward Planning Committee, 1968 (Box-folder 91: 15)
      - Reports to Forward Planning Committee, 1968 (Box-folder 91: 16)
      - Multidisciplinary studies, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 92: 1)
      - National Endowment for the Humanities proposal, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 92: 2)
      - IMB grant, Graduate Institute for Teaching, 1968-1971 (Box-folder 92: 3)
    - Black Studies
      - Material by date, 1968-1970 (Box-folder 92: 4-5)
      - Black sit-in, 1969 (Box-folder 92: 6)
      - Programs, 1969 (Box-folder 92: 7)
      - Housing, 1970 (Box-folder 92: 8)
      - General, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 92: 9)
    - Resignation
      - Official statements, 1967-1970 (Box-folder 92: 10)
      - Letters
        - Faculty and staff, 1970 (Box-folder 92: 11)
        - Alumnae, 1970 (Box-folder 92: 12)
        - Public, 1970 (Box-folder 92: 13)
        - Miscellaneous, 1970 (Box-folder 93: 1)
      - Trustee resolution to Nell Eurich, 1970 (Box-folder 93: 2)
  - National Academy of Engineering
    - "Focus on the Future: A National Action Plan for Career-Long Education for Engineers" binder, 1988 (Box-folder 93: 3)
    - Career-Long Education for Engineers (CLEFE)
      - 1988 (Box-folder 93: 4)
      - Meeting, December 1987 (Box-folder 93: 5)
      - Meeting, July 1987 (Box-folder 93: 6)
      - 1986-1987 (Box-folder 93: 7)
  - Industry and Higher Education file, 1986-1990 (Box-folder 94: 1)
    Eurich served on the editorial board
  - AT&T Bell Laboratories
    - Bell contract, 1985, undated (Box-folder 94: 2)
    - Background for Bell Academy, Program in Computer Science and Engineering, 1985 (Box-folder 94: 3)
    - Progress reports, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 94: 4)
    - Summary report, 1986 (Box-folder 94: 5)
    - Courses and evaluations, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 94: 6)
    - Hill Report, 1985 (Box-folder 94: 7)
    - University and college contracts, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 94: 8)
    - University and college computer science departments, 1985, undated (Box-folder 94: 9)
    - Report, "Advising Systems: Five Corporate Profiles,", 1986 (Box-folder 94: 10)
    - Consultants, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 94: 11)
    - General notes, 1985, undated (Box-folder 94: 12)
    - Bell Labs curriculum-related material, undated (Box-folder 94: 13)
    - Self-study course evaluations, 1986 (Box-folder 95: 1)
  - Carnegie Foundation for the Advancement of Teaching
    - General, 1977-1996 (Box-folder 95: 2)
    - Finance and Administration Committee, 1976-1978 (Box-folder 95: 3)
    - Correspondence with Ernest Boyer, 1979-1985 (Box-folder 95: 4)
    - Foundation papers, 1984 (Box-folder 95: 5)
    - Distinguished leadership citation (Box-folder 95: 6)
      Framed award
- Corporate Classrooms file
  - Strategic Council, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 95: 7-8)
  - Manuscript file
    - Sources and bibliography, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 96: 1)
    - Style sheet, 1984 (Box-folder 96: 2)
    - Outlines, 1981-1983 (Box-folder 96: 3)
    - Fact sheets, undated (Box-folder 96: 4)
    - Final draft, 1985 (Box-folder 96: 5)
      Annotated, without bibliography
  - Chapter 1
    - Notes, undated (Box-folder 96: 6)
    - Why corporations invest in education, 1976-1984 (Box-folder 96: 7)
    - Size and amount, 1977-1984 (Box-folder 96: 8)
    - Training programs and tuition plans, Bureau of National Affairs, 1978, undated (Box-folder 96: 9)
  - Chapter 2
    - Notes, 1958-1982, undated (Box-folder 96: 10)
    - National Association of Corporation Schools, 1928, undated (Box-folder 96: 11)
  - Chapter 3
    - References, 1980-1983, undated (Box-folder 96: 12)
    - Notes, undated (Box-folder 96: 13)
  - Chapter 4
    - References, 1976-1984 (Box-folder 96: 14)
    - Curriculum, content, undated (Box-folder 96: 15)
  - Chapter 5
    - Notes, undated (Box-folder 97: 1)
  - Chapter 6
    - Notes and clippings, 1981-1984 (Box-folder 97: 2)
    - Legislation, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 97: 3)
  - General
    - Notes and facts in regards to 1985 January 15 draft, undated (Box-folder 97: 4)
    - Types of corporations, Fortune 500 list, 1984, undated (Box-folder 97: 5)
    - General notes on corporate classrooms and programs, 1983-1985, undated (Box-folder 97: 6)
  - Corporate training programs
    - Clippings on corporate colleges, 1981 (Box-folder 97: 7)
    - American Institute of Banking, 1981 (Box-folder 97: 8)
    - Atlantic Richfield Company (ARCO), 1982-1988 (Box-folder 97: 9)
    - AT&T Communications, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 97: 10)
    - Bell Systems, 1982, undated (Box-folder 98: 1)
    - Control Data Corporation, 1981-1984 (Box-folder 98: 2)
    - Con Edison, 1983 (Box-folder 98: 3)
    - Digital Equipment Corporation, 1983 (Box-folder 98: 4)
- The Learning Industry and Adult Learning Project file
  - Vendors
    - Programs
      - Technical workers
        - Allen-Bradley, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 98: 5)
        - GMI Engineering and Management Institute
          - Catalogs and descriptive materials, 1987-1988, undated (Box-folder 98: 6)
          - Course announcements, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 99: 1)
        - John Wiley & Sons, 1986-1988 (Box-folder 99: 2)
        - TPC Training Systems, 1987-1989 (Box-folder 99: 3)
        - University Associates, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 99: 4)
        - Other companies, A to G, 1987, undated (Box-folder 99: 5)
        - Other companies, I to V, 1987-1989 (Box-folder 99: 6)
      - Managers
        - Articles and other literature, 1985-1991 (Box-folder 99: 7)
        - American Management Association (AMA)
          - Magazines and reports, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 100: 1)
          - Catalogs, 1986-1989 (Box-folder 100: 2)
          - Course brochures
            - General management, 1987 (Box-folder 100: 3)
            - Management skills, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 100: 4)
            - Fiscal skills, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 100: 5)
            - Personnel issues, 1987 (Box-folder 100: 6)
            - Training skills, 1986-1988 (Box-folder 100: 7)
            - Self-study, 1987, undated (Box-folder 100: 8)
          - Book catalogs and conferences, 1988, undated (Box-folder 100: 9)
        - Britannica, 1991, undated (Box-folder 100: 10)
        - Center for Creative Leadership, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 100: 11)